WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - Night Watch Programs: 1 thru 14, with host Peter Lee, 1975; wsyr_radio_701; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 79:20 (Box 34)
    Originals without commercials, 5:40 each. Show 1: Julie's Living Death; Show 2: George’s Private Portrait; Show 3: The Manner’s Dream House, Chard; Show 4: Tom & Christy, Snowed in in the Adirondacks; Show 5: Minnie Kline’s Cut Out; Show 6: Dead Ship; Show 7: The Initiation; Show 8: Thundering Train; Show 9: Killed in the Cornfield; Show 10: Mrs. Smart and the German; Show 11: Dreams of Charles Leonard Evan Morgan; Show 12: Lenny’s Problem; Show 13: Jenny Willam’s Kittens; Show 14: The New Mary
  - Night Watch Programs: 103 thru 115, 1975; wsyr_radio_708; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    103: Aunt Margaret; 104: The Experiment; 105: Skylight; 106: Dream Girl; 107: Practical Joker Ruddy; 108: The Rivals; 109: Maddy’s Plants; 110: Mom’s Nightmare; 111: Friends; 112: Mrs. Fitzsimmon’s Seance in Reserve; 113: No Man Is An Island; 114: His Phobia’s; 115: Dorothy’s Jealousy
  - Night Watch Programs: 15 through 27, with host Peter Lee, 1975; wsyr_radio_702; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    15: The Knife; 16: Harry’s Heart; 17a: calibration tone; 17b: Wally’s Imagination; 18: Chris’s Fate; 19: Squeaky Clean; 20: The Elevator; 21: Killed by Her Own Hand; 22: Unfair Reward; 23: Professor Johnston’s Plants; 24: Misplaced Fears; 25: The Rescue; 26: Forest Stroll; 27: Ed’s Plane
  - Night Watch Programs: 28 thru 40, with host Peter Lee, 1975; wsyr_radio_703; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    (Key: W - Week; P - Program; S - Script) 28: The Brigadier; 29: Harriett’s [sic] Complaints; 30: The Terror Lives On; 31: John Hart (W-7, P-1, S-11); 32: The Invitation - The Wind (W-7, P-3, S-41); 33: Burning Again (W-7, P-5, S-14); 34: Lover’s Park; 35: The Mirror; 36: The waves; 37: Perfect Couple; 38: Jackie’s Guilt; 39: Tommy Jordon’s Bees; 40: Die Baby Die (W-10, P-1, S-40).
  - Night Watch Programs: 41 thru 53, 1975; wsyr_radio_704; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    (Key: W - Week; P - Program; S - Script) 41: (W-10, P-3, S-27), Rebecca the Seamstress; 42: (W-10, P-5, S-53), Justice?; 43: (W-11, P-1, S-20), Respect Ghosts!; 44: (W-11, P-3, S-18), Collin’s Fear of Trees; 45: (W-11, P-5, S-26), Nine Mishaps; 46: (W-12, P-1, S-33), Manny’s Dreams; 47: (W-12, P-3, S-25), The Amhearst’s Paintings; 48: (W-12, P-5, S-52), Janet’s Books; 49: (W-13, P-1, S-54), The Sauna; 50: (W-13, P-3, S-22), The Stolen Flowers; 51: (W-13, P-5, S-58), Captain Clyde & Charlie; 52: (W-?, P-?, S-?), Calibration Tone & Paw Paw Tucker; 53: (W-?, P-?, S-?), Calibration Tone & Paul’s Breakdown
  - Night Watch Programs: 54 thru 66, 1975; wsyr_radio_705; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    54: Calibration Tone - Giles and Clair; 55: David Randall, The Curse; 56: Rebellious Walden House; 57: Robin - Parachute Death; 58: Physic Art Murder; 59: Rattlesnake; 60: Pacific Crest Trail; 61: Cleaning Up the City; 62: Johnny’s Claustrophobia; 63: The Laird of Kinlessit (sp?), Justice for Joe McCullough; 64: Why the Braithwaits [sic] Never Came Home; 65: Calibration Tone - Philip’s Choice; 66: Sea Monster
  - Night Watch Programs: 67 thru 79, 1975; wsyr_radio_706; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    67: Gas Attendant; 68: The Crows; 69: Peppered Witch; 70: Grandfather Clock; 71: Baby Murderer; 72: Promo Intro: Claus Ulrick’s Internal Fear (W-20, d-2, story 70); 73: Promo Intro: Lies; 74: Dave’s Madness; 75: The Pike; 76: Calibration Tone - The Fortune Teller (Egg Reader), Carol’s Fortune; 77: Calibration Tone: The Castle; 78: Calibration Tone - Dan Arthur’s Jealousy, What Dan Wished For; 79: Calibration Tone - The Buck
  - Night Watch Programs: 80 thru 102, 1975; wsyr_radio_707; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
    80: a. Calibration Tone; b. (Program levels start low, improve at 2:12), Harry’s Escape; (81 thru 90 missing); 91: Avalanche; 92: The Beautiful House with a Dog; 93: One Mistake; 94: Gardart’s Rats; 95: Finished By a Tanker; 96: Rifle Butt; 97: (W-24, P-2), Mugger Paranoia; 98: The Spiders; 99: Stress Poison; 100: The Tattoo; 101: The Perfectionist; 102: Convict’s Tunnell [sic]
  - Nightwatch - Week 12, Programs 46-48, 06/01/1975; wsyr_radio_521; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    Pgm 1 - Script 33 - Manny’s Dreams Of Death; Pgm 3 - Script 25 - The Amherst’s Pictures; Pgm 5 - Script 5 - Janet’s Book.
  - Nightwatch - Week 13 - programs 49-51, 06/08/1975; wsyr_radio_522; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    Pgm 1 - Script 54; 49 - Sauna Death - Scr. 54, Pgm. 1; 50 - Graveyard Flowers - Scrp. 22, Pgm. 3; 51 - Civil War - Script 58 - Pgm. 5.
  - Nightwatch - Week 15 - programs 55-57, 06/20/1975; wsyr_radio_524; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Pgm. 55, Script 5 - David Randall - The Curse; Pgm. 56, Script 6 - Rebellious Walden House; Pgm. 57, Script 35 - Robin - Parachute Death.
  - Nightwatch - Week 16 - programs 58-60, 06/27/1975; wsyr_radio_525; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Pgm 1-58, Script 2 - Psychic Apt. Murder; Pgm 3-59, Script 36 - Rattlesnake; Pgm 5-60, Script 55 - Pacific Crest Trail.
  - Nightwatch - Week 17 - programs 61-63, 07/04/1975; wsyr_radio_526; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Pgm. 61-1, Script 47: Killer Street Cleaner; Pgm. 62-3, Script 23: Johnny - Claustrophobia; Pgm. 63-5, Script 10: Joe McCullough - Dungeon.
  - Nightwatch - Week 22 - programs 86-90, 08/17/1975; wsyr_radio_527; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Program 1-86, Script 84: Piranha Fish; Program 2-87, Script 78: Appleyard House; Program 3-88, Script 74: Baby Sitter; Program 4-89, Script 73: Jane Loring - Coastline; Program 5-90, Script 67: Suicide - Impaling.
  - Nightwatch - Week 23 - programs 91-95, 08/24/1975; wsyr_radio_528; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    91: Helicopter Avalanche; 92: Canine Ghost; 93: Nitro Glycerin; 94: Rat Exterminator; 95: Fishing Boat
  - Nightwatch - Week 24 - programs 96-100, 08/31/1975; wsyr_radio_529; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Pgm 96-1: Gun Butt; Pgm 97-2: Mugger Paranoia; Pgm 98-3: Killer Spiders; Pgm 99-4: Dieter’s Heart Attack; Pgm 100-5: Dentist.
  - Nightwatch - Week 26 - programs 101-103, 09/07/1975; wsyr_radio_530; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    Pgm 1-101, Script 98: The Perfectionist; Pgm 3-102, Script 97: Convict’s Tunnel; Pgm 5-103, Script 103: Aunt Margaret.
  - Nightwatch - Week 27 - programs 104-106, 1975; wsyr_radio_531; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    1-104: Man Mouse - Script 99; 3-105: Tom & Skylight; 5-106: Dream Girl - Script 104.
  - Nightwatch - Week 28 - programs 107-109, 09/21/1975; wsyr_radio_532; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    1-107: Practical Joker - Script 108; 3-108: Rival Gardener - Script 106; 5-109: Maddy’s Plants - Script 105.
  - Nightwatch - Week 29 - programs 110-112, wsyr_radio_533; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    1-110: Mother-Son Nightmare - Scr. 107; 3-111: Graveyard - Scr. 109; 5-112: Medium In Reverse - Scr. 110.
  - Nightwatch - Week 30 - programs 113-115, 10/05/1975; wsyr_radio_534; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
    1-113: No Man Is An Island - Scr. 113; 3-114: Bridge Jumper - Scr. 112; 5-115: Twins - Scr. 111.
  - Nightwatch - Week 5 - Programs 21-25, 04/13/1975; wsyr_radio_517; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    Program (#1) #21 "Terror In India"; Program (#2) #22 "The Hazards of Restoring a Haunted House," "The Ghost in the Old House"; Program (#3) #23 "Do you talk to your plant?" "Prof. Johnson & his Begonia," "The Jealous Plant"; Program (#4) #24 "A Fear of Fire - A Death by Water," "Fire & Water"; Program (#5) #25 "A Mediterranean Holiday," "A Cliff-Hanger," "Death on a Mediterranean Hiway."
  - Nightwatch - Week 7, 1975; wsyr_radio_519; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    #3 - W-7, P-3, S-41 - "Alka Seltzer," "One A Day Vitamins," "Elaine & Wind," "World Wildlife Foundation;" #4 - W-7, P-4, S-13 - "One A Day Vitamins," "Snowed In In The Adirondacks," "U.S. Navy," (Sweetheart Corners Office); "Also W-1, P-4."
  - Nightwatch - Week14 - programs 52-54, 06/13/1975; wsyr_radio_523; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    Program #52, Mon. 6/9 - script 64, Quicksand; Program #53, Wed. 6/11 - script 62, Paul Dicken-Salesman; Program #54, Fri. 6/13 - script 30, Fat People.
  - Nightwatch Programs 26-30 (Week 6), 04/18/1975; wsyr_radio_518; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    #1 Program 26: "A Dead end forest path," "A Strange Forest," "Forest Labyrinth;" #2 Program 27: "The Beautiful Plan - Happily Ever After;" #3 Program 28: "The Brigadier’s Weakness;" #4 Program 29: "Harriet’s Perfect Housekeeper;" #5 Program 30: "The Terror Lives On (Dave & Johnny)."
  - Nightwatch Programs 40-42 (Week 10), 05/18/1975; wsyr_radio_520; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    1 - Pgm 40, Script 40 - "Miss Edward's’ Dilemma - Die Baby Die;" 2 - Pgm 41, Script 27 - "Rebecca’s Needles;" 3 - Pgm 42, #5 Script 53 - "Charles Hobby."
  - Nightwatch Programs 6-10 (week 2), wsyr_radio_516; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
    #1 Program 6, Script 15, "The Death Ship"; #2 Program 7, Script 21, "The Champions’ Club"; #3 Program 8, Script 59, "The Subway Follower"; #4 Program 9, Script 47, "Alabama Summer"; #5 Program 10, Script 38, "Terror in the London Blitz"
  - Nixon - Foreign Policy, 03/16/1971; wsyr_radio_488; NBC News Network Feed.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 15)
  - Nixon: Presidential Address - Troop Withdrawal from Vietnam, April 7, 1971; wsyr_radio_975; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:45 (Box 56)
  - Normandy today: [William Watts] Chaplin; R. C. A. Music America loves best, 06/03/1945; 06/06/1945; wsyr_radio_248; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Nuclear Non Proliferation Treaty Signing (Lyndon Johnson), 07/01/1968; wsyr_radio_483; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
    1 - Johnson 7/1/68 Signing of Nuclear Treat, NBC Radio Network Feed; 2 - BBC Shortwave fragment, Radio Newsreel 1968, World Service
  - Opponents of State-control "Tidelands Oil", 04/17/1953; wsyr_radio_100; includes discussion by Senators Lehman, Hill, Tobey. UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - Organ Music Pipe and Electronic, wsyr_radio_935; compilation tape with music mostly from phono records made by Norman R. Seeburger for Allan Milair; list of titles in box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 53)
  - Our Community, 02/17/1973; wsyr_radio_715; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community - Bishop Ned Cole, 06/30/1974; wsyr_radio_508; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 16)
  - Our Community - C.N.Y. Humane Association, 07/21/1974; wsyr_radio_511; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:53 (Box 17)
  - Our Community - Careers, 07/28/1974; wsyr_radio_512; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 17)
  - Our Community - Free Enterprise, 09/22/1974; wsyr_radio_513; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Our Community - Nurse Practitioner Program - Dr. Heur; Fay Whitney, wsyr_radio_614; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Our Community - Onondaga Council On Alcoholism, 07/07/1974; wsyr_radio_509; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 16)
  - Our Community - Preservation of City History Buildings, 02/16/1975; wsyr_radio_515; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 17)
  - Our Community - School and Racial Balance, 02/09/1975; wsyr_radio_514; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:55 (Box 17)
  - Our Community P.B. - Glenn Brown: Executive Director of Peace, Inc., 06/02/1974; wsyr_radio_507; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:00 (Box 16)
  - Our Community, guest: John Mungovin, Model Cities Director, Playback date: 02/4/1973; 12:05-12:30 PM. Recorded: 01/29/1973; wsyr_radio_714; hosts G. Roberts & D. Edwards; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: American Cancer Society - Mr. Harvey Tucker, Chairman, Service and Rehabilitation and Joan Apple, Chairman of Bike-A-Thon, 09/30/1973; wsyr_radio_736; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Animal Control, Gany Senamo [?] and guests, recorded: 12/28/1973; playback 12/30/1973; wsyr_radio_744; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Annabel Davis and Mrs. Earl Munderback - R. S. V. P. (Retired and Senior Volunteer Program) volunteers, with D. Edwards and John Nicholson, 10/19/1973; 10/28/1973; wsyr_radio_739; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Better Business Bureau, Bill Lukas, Dick Modest [?] and Mrs. Kobealine [?], 01/27/1974; wsyr_radio_749; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Bilingual Studies, Spanish Speaking Community, guests: Dr. Robert Diflorio, Co-ordinator Special Needs Program; Mr. Jack Barry, Co-ordinator West Side; Mrs. Viola Feliz, parent and teacher [illegible]; Luiz Gonzalez (10 years old), student (Preso Ricar [?]), 01/06/1974; wsyr_radio_747; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:49 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Bill Lape, Pat O’Brien: Syracuse Symphony - Haas; Pranzwitz, recorded 08/17/1973; broadcasted 09/09/1973; wsyr_radio_734; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Bob Kelly, Executive Director Retail Gasoline Dealers of Central New York, 03/03/1974; wsyr_radio_750; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Bottle Legislation, Jim Karp, Mrs. Worden, Mrs. Elizabeth Mosher, 04/21/1974; wsyr_radio_757; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:47 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Cerebral Palsy Center, Frank Sirianni, Ruth Doyle, Miss Teresa Crane, 03/03/1974; wsyr_radio_751; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Connie Timberlake, playback Sunday 08/11/1974, 08/18/1974; wsyr_radio_762; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:20 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Cooperative Extension Service, William Quinn, Linda McChristal, Mery Ellen Downing, hosts: George Roberts and Jerry Barsha, 05/12/1974; wsyr_radio_759; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Doctor Geo. Bragle of Empire State College and student, 12/02/1973; wsyr_radio_742; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Dr. Lee Porter, University College, recorded 06/07/1973, playback: Sunday 06/17/1973; wsyr_radio_726; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:25 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Drug Abuse, Don. Edwards, Geo. Roberts, Father Buckel, Mr. Holness, Youth Director PEACE Incorporated, 08/19/1973; wsyr_radio_732; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Father For Champlin, Don Edwards, G. Roberts, 07/22/1973; wsyr_radio_729; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:05 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Fire Prevention in Onondaga City, guest: Mr. Mike Waters, recorded 01/03/1975; playback 01/05/1975; wsyr_radio_770; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: First Methodist Church - Fifteenth Anniversary, Richard Troendle and Rev. Irving Hill, 03/31/1974; 12/31/0000; wsyr_radio_754; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:57 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: G. Roberts - D. Edwards, National Guard, 08/12/1973; wsyr_radio_731; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Guest Dr. Donald Boudrough [?], 07/08/1973; wsyr_radio_727; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:10 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Guest: James Miller, Vice President Niagara Mohawk, 05/20/1973; wsyr_radio_723; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Heart Problems, Dr. Duggan with Don Edwards, Geo Roberts, 11/11/1973; wsyr_radio_740; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Howard Messing Director of City Consumer Affairs with Don Edwards and John Nicholson, 04/14/1974; wsyr_radio_756; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Internal Revenue, Interview, 02/25/1973; wsyr_radio_716; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:36 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: JEMCO Jordan- Elbridge Medical Project, guests: John Eagan and Dick Rounds, 11/10/1974; wsyr_radio_766; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:05 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Josiah Coleman - Careers, 05/27/1973; wsyr_radio_724; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Josiah Coleman, Careers Incorporated, G. Roberts and J. Bowles, 01/10/1974; 01/13/1974; wsyr_radio_748; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:55 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Judge Heath, Town of Clay, playback Sunday, 05/13/1973; recorded 05/10/1973; wsyr_radio_722; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Loretto Geriatric Center, guests: Norman E. Harper; Nancy H. Bolton, 09/29/1974; wsyr_radio_763; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Mary Peagram [sic], Director Dunbar Center, Mary Felton, 05/19/1974; wsyr_radio_760; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: MDAA Interviews, Sunday, March 18, 1973; wsyr_radio_718; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:40 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Metropolitan Commission on Aging, Miss Ann Babie, Director, Mrs. Ros Bilford, Vice Chairman, 11/24/1974; wsyr_radio_768; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Monsignor Eckerman, Principal of Bishop Ludden High School, recorded 08/24/1973; broadcast 09/02/1973; wsyr_radio_733; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 24:00 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Monsignor Thomas Costello and Sister Gvomy [?], Feb 24 [no year]; wsyr_radio_773; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 41)
  - Our Community: Mr. Andrew Willis, Executive Director of The Urban League of Onondaga County, 04/15/1973; wsyr_radio_721; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Mr. Eric Dressler, County Consumer, 03/25/1973; wsyr_radio_719; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:35 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Mr. Richard Neave, Meteorologist in charge National Weather Service, Hancock Field, 06/10/1973; wsyr_radio_725; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Nuclear Power, Dr. Meyer, 04/28/1974; wsyr_radio_758; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Nurse Practitioner Program, guests: Alice Chico, Assistant Professor of Nursing Upstate Medical Center, Dr. Neil Kay, Upstate Medical Center, recorded January 31, 1975; playback February 2, 1975.; wsyr_radio_772; reel No. B-26; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 41)
  - Our Community: Obscenity, Carl Guy, Anti Pornography Commission, Dan Casey, President American Library Association, 03/22/1974; 03/24/1974; wsyr_radio_753; note on box reads "Edited by order of Shurle [?]"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Office Fuel Allocation Gasoline Shortage Discussion, Dennis Jones, 03/10/1974; wsyr_radio_752; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:55 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Our American Heritage, 10/20/1974; wsyr_radio_765; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Paul Drescula, American Cancer Society, 07/15/1973; wsyr_radio_728; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:40 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Pioneer Activities Center - Handicapped, Mrs. lane Hubbard, Mrs. Nancy Kraft, Mr. Ronald La France, 04/05/1974; 04/07/1974; wsyr_radio_755; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Reach Out, Robert Detor, Rich Sanchez [?], Jim Bass, recorded October 4, 1974; playback: October 6, 1974; wsyr_radio_764; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Red Cross, Mr. Gilbert Tills, Dr. Eugene Lozner, 09/23/1973; wsyr_radio_735; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Retarded Children, Interview Dr. Collis, 08/05/1973; wsyr_radio_730; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:51 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Richard Flynn, Vice President Consumer Relations of Niagara Mohawk Power corporation, 12/16/1973; wsyr_radio_743; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:40 (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Rosemary Pooler, Director of P. I. R. G., Fifth District Counsel, 01/12/1975; wsyr_radio_771; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:05 (Box 41)
  - Our Community: Shelley Turian of Syracuse City Consumer Division, 04/01/1973; wsyr_radio_720; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Suburban Education, guests: Mr. Phillips, Mr. Mayer, recorded 11/15/1974; playback 11/17/1974; wsyr_radio_767; reel No. B-4; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Syracuse, The Crossroad of New York, John Spencer, narrator, Frank Thompson, narrator, Bill Roseboom, 10/14/1973; wsyr_radio_738; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:20 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Transportation Bond Issue, Mr. Powers and Mr. Shub, 10/07/1973; wsyr_radio_737; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: United Way, guests - Mark De Michele, Bill Scofield, 05/26/1974; wsyr_radio_761; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Unity Acres (Orwell, New York), guest: Father Armani, Sunday, March 4, 1973; wsyr_radio_717; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:40 (Box 37)
  - Our Community: Unwanted Children - Walter Driscoll, Executive Director Catholic Services, Mrs. Amelie Griener [sic], Director Home Aids Central New York, Don Edwards, J. Barsha (part 2), 11/25/1973; 09/10/1972; wsyr_radio_745; note in box reads: Dr. Harry Morgan, Afro Studies, Syracuse University; Warner Wims, Cooperative College Center; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Our Community: Unwanted Children - Walter Driscoll, Executive Director Catholic Services, Sister Constance Egan, Catholic Chaplin [sic], Family Court, Don Edwards, J. Barsha (part 1), 11/18/1973; wsyr_radio_741; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 38)
  - Our Community: Upstate Medical Center Bazaar [?] to benefit Coronary Unit, guests: Lori Sigman, Nancy Gilman, Kathy Gary, 12/08/1974; wsyr_radio_769; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 40)
  - Our Community: Volunteer Center, guests - Mrs. Caroline Ruhe and Mrs. Gail Davis, 11/04/1973; wsyr_radio_746; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:55 (Box 39)
  - "Our Community" - Consolidated Industries, 03/07/1973; wsyr_radio_497; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 16)
  - "Our Community" - Home Care For The Elderly, 04/22/1973; wsyr_radio_498; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - "Our Community" - Suburban Crime, 02/11/1973; wsyr_radio_496; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:30 (Box 15)
  - "Our Community" - WSYR - Pompeion Players - Monsignor Charles Borguionni, 04/29/1973; wsyr_radio_499; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Page one: Special Interview with Stanley S. Scott, Special Assistant to the President Nixon, with Baker Morten, host, 10/21/1973; 11/18/1973; wsyr_radio_987; note in box reads: "Playback: Sunday, November 18, 1973, 9:35-9:55 PM, on WSYR-AM & FM." Tape must be edited at head end ... announcer intro and close needed using their music bed. Close cue: This is Baker Morten in Washington; plus music bed out at 19:37.; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:00 (Box 57)
  - Parliament war meeting - "First day of war" (Part 1), 09/01/1939; 09/03/1939; wsyr_radio_112; MBS - Intl 8:30 PM, Cut end, #2.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pearl Harbor - Interview - [Jim] Wahl, 12/04/1945; wsyr_radio_270; boys and girls from Syracuse are interviewed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pearl Harbor Day - Jim Wahl, 12/07/1944; wsyr_radio_234; Jim Wahl, who was present at the time of the attack, reflects on it and the importance of buying war bonds; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pearl Harbor Day (parts 1 and 3), 12/07/1944; wsyr_radio_232; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Pearl Harbor Day (parts 2 and 4), 12/07/1944; wsyr_radio_233; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Phone interview with Master Sargeant Shaw from Valley Forge; Hickox luncheon (both sides), 05/13/1953; wsyr_radio_409; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 2 has no label. Dubbed from tape. Cut 1 - Don Daver interviews master Sergeant Shaw, Korean War; Cut 2 Hickox lunchon - "Corporal Bob Hickox Day", "Sgt. Bob Shaw Day"; " Put. first class Peter Le Clair Day"; Mayor Tom. J. Corcoran - speaks, introduced by E. R. Vadeboncouer. "Armed Forces week", Wed. May 13, 1953. Continued on Side 2 (without label), ends with applause.